Come on, quick.
Officer.
- Officer, stop that person!
- Ms. An Yun-su?
- Do something! In the black hoodie!
- Ma'am, I need you to stay calm.
- Grab her!
- Wait! Over there!
Stay calm!
Look! In the black hoodie!
Please, you gotta listen!
What's wrong with her?
I need you to calm down!
You gotta stop them!
Don't let them get away!
You… gotta stop them.
That's my husband's killer.
Everybody out! Let's move it!
Hurry up, ladies.
Hurry up!
Face the wall!
Let's go!
Move it!
Line up outside. Now!
- We don't have all day. Let's go!
- Hurry. Let's move. Chop-chop.
Don't turn around.
Let's count.
- One.
- Three.
- Four.
- Five.
1605.
Let's go!
1605!
What?
Get outside, now.
Check over there.
Server's down, so we haven't
been recording for a while.
And who was on solitary duty?
Officer Jung was, but she's off duty now.
Seriously?
CWCU
PROSECUTOR BAEK DONG-HUN
UNDERAGE ONLINE GAMBLING SITE
OPERATION CASE
GU HUI-YEONG, AGE 17
INTERVIEW AT 3 P.M. ON 26TH
DETECTIVE RYU JI-SU
Yes, talk to me.
Sir, hi. Ryu Ji-su here.
I thought you'd wanna hear about this.
An Yun-su broke probation
and left the house.
Apparently, someone came into her yard,
and she went after them.
MO EUN MISSING FROM DETENTION
AS OF 10:30 P.M.
Yes, Officer Bae. Hi.
Is she hurt?
I see. Uh, I'll be right there, okay?
Yeah.
Mr. Jang, I think you should stop by
Ms. An's house first.
She said that Sop
is all by herself at home.
Some officers are on their way there,
and she's afraid that Sop will be scared
if she sees them.
- Uh, sir. Who are you?
- I'm An Yun-su's attorney.
Hold on a minute. You're her attorney?
The lights. Turn them off.
The whole neighborhood's about to wake up.
- Put me down! Let go of me!
- It's okay.
- We're gonna go see Mommy.
- Put me down!
Are you serious right now?
- You're gonna go see Mommy.
- Put me down!
- Sop, I'm here.
- You're okay. You're…
Everything's fine. I got her.
There. Sop, it's me. I'm sorry.
I got you.
Look at the CCTV from the center.
Mo Eun's gotta be in there.
Keep an eye out for her. Got it?
I heard what happened,
and I understand it was a tough situation.
But as protocol says,
probation violations
are ours to deal with.
Yeah, I don't think so.
We'll be bringing her in
for obstruction of justice
and assaulting a law enforcement officer.
Listen, this is not as easy
as you might think, all right?
A single report can change a lot.
It has the power to ruin someone's life.
Is that some kind of manipulation?
Huh? Come on.
You want me to ignore a clear offense
out of compassion. Is that it?
What I'm saying is that you should try
to go at it differently.
Come to a rational decision.
Wow, you can't be serious.
Oh.
I told you to watch the kid,
not bring her here!
Keep it down, or you'll wake her up.
You brought Sop all the way out here?
She cried the whole time
and fell asleep just now.
Could you please get me out of these?
Would you mind removing the cuffs?
She's not gonna run
with her child being here.
- And who are you?
- This is Ms. An Yun's lawyer.
Is that right?
Yes.
Take them off. Go ahead.
Yes, sir.
I'll be back in a minute.
From now on, talk to me.
Yeah, understood.
- Please do something!
- Look, you see that?
Her pushing and assaulting officers?
Ms. An!
Look! In the black hoodie!
- Hold her down!
- Ma'am, I need you to calm down!
You gotta stop them!
Don't let them get away!
God.
As you just saw,
we were simply following procedure
in making the arrest.
There. Plain as day.
Plain as day?
I mean, look at how many of you there are.
Why would you even consider
assaulting her?
That woman is coming at us
and starts grabbing.
What else do you wanna call that?
We can argue about it all you want.
There's one thing
I don't understand though.
Why is it that nobody ever tried
to hear my client out?
Look, the goal was to make an arrest.
Nobody was there to hear her out.
So you admit you ignored my client?
She's wearing an ankle monitor,
accused of murdering her own husband.
Why should we listen to someone like that?
What's the point?
Officer, are you willing
to put those exact words in your report?
Why do you want me to do that, huh?
It proves you were just out
to get my client.
And the last thing you needed
was a proper reason to do so.
- Goddamn it.
- Hold on.
What am I looking at?
Just another thing you missed.
She says someone was watching the house,
which is why she ran out of it
in the first place,
but the police refused to hear about it.
- So you need proof of that.
- Yes.
I'll see what I can find,
but you should go to Ms. An.
It's clear there was an intruder and that
my client went chasing after them.
Her altercation with the police
will be seen as self-defense
and not assault.
Agreed?
Or you prefer to have the police
exposed for negligence?
Is that how you wanna go?
Make it public
and see what the people think?
I, uh…
It's not our jurisdiction anyway,
so feel free to take her,
and then you can file your own report.
I don't know
why you're giving me that look.
We were honestly just there for support.
How sad.
Going through all that trouble
only to get flak for it in the end.
It must be weird for you.
All right. Good work.
Hey, don't forget this!
Is that ours?
Wow.
That really makes my anklet look prettier.
Thank you, baby.
Here too?
Thank you so much.
How did it go?
It went fine.
Rest a little, and you'll be good to go.
Fine? What do you mean?
Uh, tonight's incident
will be reported to the court.
Uh…
We'll have to wait and see if the judge
is willing to consider
the extenuating circumstances.
Well, I'm pretty sure they will
once they've read the report
that Sun-deok is gonna write.
That I am?
I'm just gonna describe what happened.
Just what we need, the facts. Period.
It should be enough, right?
Yeah.
Uh, I'll postpone next week's meeting.
Just come by the office
once you've been discharged
and are feeling better.
We don't need to reschedule.
Um, do you mind if we head home?
Sop, we're leaving.
Oh, are you okay to go?
Yeah, it's fine.
Ah, really?
Hi there!
You must be Sop.
You like chocolate milk? Look at that.
Wanna have some with me?
I told you not to follow strangers.
Remember?
Ms. An Yun-su.
MO EUN MISSING FROM DETENTION
AS OF 10:30 P.M.
Who were you running after?
Who was it?
Aren't you getting paid
to figure that out?
That's right, which is why I wanna know
who you thought you were pursuing.
Someone came into her yard
and managed to peer into the house.
Someone wearing a black hoodie.
How was she supposed to react?
She's clearly the victim here.
Why do you insist on being so rude to her?
Let's go, Sop.
This way.
DAEUN HOSPITAL
It's on the flash drive.
All right.
Dashcam footage from the police car.
You already knew they'd found Mo Eun.
So why did you do it?
I wanted to see how An Yun-su would react.
I wanted to know how much influence
Mo Eun has over her while she's in jail.
I was curious.
Doctor!
It was an emergency.
She'd gone into shock from a spider bite.
I just gave her something
to calm her down, and she fell asleep.
Asleep for how long?
She took the meds
about three hours ago, so--
Not her.
I meant you.
Oh, me?
I just passed out a little.
I had been up all night.
Did I do something wrong?
The guards took Mo Eun
to the infirmary but forgot to log it.
They say it's a pretty common mistake.
Oh, another thing.
It appears that during the time
she was gone, all the CCTV cameras
were coincidentally down.
It seems there was
a server error or something.
Do you believe that anything
could have happened during that time?
Not according to Ms. Eom,
and I couldn't really press any further.
It felt like I would be overstepping.
I see. Thank you so much, Mr. Jin.
You did all the work, really.
Oh, and please tell Ms. An
not to worry too much.
I will.
How did you do it?
Was it really you,
or did you hire someone else?
I'll only believe what I've seen.
What I've seen with my own eyes.
By the way, Yun-su…
even if you do get out,
don't get any funny ideas
'cause I will keep an eye on you
no matter where you are or what you do.
Our deal comes with an expiration date.
You'll have to meet the requirement
before your appeal trial begins.
If you hesitate and miss the deadline,
I'll retract my confession
while I'm on the stand at your trial.
Then you'll end up back here,
crumbling under the world's harassment
all over again.
And your daughter will grow up alone,
resenting you for the rest of her life.
There's only one way
for you to clear your name
and be reunited with your daughter.
How did you do it?
Ironic, isn't it?
In order to be acquitted of murder,
you have to
do one yourself.
I've heard that mothers,
they would do
absolutely anything for their child.
Is that true?
What about you, Yun-su?
Do you
have what it takes?
407, you're going back to the shared cell.
The other inmates have been whispering,
saying the Witch
pulled some kind of trick last night.
You caused all that trouble,
and somehow, you look refreshed.
Thanks to those meds I got,
I slept like a baby.
We're moving you back to the shared cells
following your attorney's request.
Can you bear living with other people?
I really can't tell.
Do you worry about them,
or is it me you're afraid of?
Hard to say.
Uh-huh.
I'm Mo Eun, and I hope we can be friends.
Ah!
Here.
You can use this locker.
She moved to another cell this morning.
Hmm?
Hello.
We've met before. Right?
In the yard.
My name's Pudgy.
Hi, nice to meet you.
I'm… I'm Jennifer.
Holy shit! What's going on?
What's with all the introductions?
Who's that? Who is that?
- Fuck.
- The Witch.
I mean, it's Mo Eun.
The Witch?
Oh. Wow.
Oh, you're the one
who got Ms. Art Teacher out?
Hey, you seem a little small though.
And you want me to believe
you killed someone
with those chopstick arms of yours?
I shouldn't have said that, right?
Anyway, we're gonna rub shoulders
for a bit, and that's it.
Yeah, unless you mess with me.
Let me clarify.
As long as no one starts anything first,
nothing will happen, right?
Yes.
Hello. I'm Wal-sun.
You got such a pretty face.
Your eyes, nose, lips.
They're just perfect.
You're just so pretty.
You should be Ms. Korea.
Mm. Well, damn.
Don't you think they should throw
a beauty pageant for girls like her, huh?
You'd be unbeatable.
- They would give you prizes.
- You need a pillow.
Here.
It's not me! Please! You gotta stop them!
Don't let them get away!
- Stand down, please.
- That's my husband's killer!
It's not me! Please!
You gotta stop them!
Don't let them get away!
Ms. An!
- Hold her down.
- That's my husband's killer.
"That's my…"
- You have violated probation.
- That's my husband's killer.
"Husband's killer."
Interesting.
That's my husband's killer.
The hooded suspect…
is real?
There.
You see the person entering the station?
Right there.
The police lost track of them
once they joined the crowd.
They say it could be a paparazzi
or some clout-chasing streamer on YouTube.
The type that goes after people
like you for attention.
We need to find that person.
Reports have been sent out,
so now we wait.
I need to know where they are.
Ms. An, if you're still worried,
I can ask them to patrol in your area.
It's fine.
I don't need that.
It's like they vanished or something.
Which means they probably changed outfits
while they were in that crowd.
That seems likely.
But what I don't understand is
why would someone go to such lengths
when all they did
was peek into someone's house?
When things get hazy,
always start by ruling out what's unclear.
Then we'll find the truth.
So what are we looking for here?
Signs that the women
struck a deal together.
Your husband's alma mater
reached out to me about his art show.
They wanna turn the one he was working on
into a memorial exhibition.
They said his final piece
was in his studio
and asked if you could bring it to them.
Open your eyes.
No, please stay with me.
Don't close your eyes, Ki-dae. Come on.
Help us! I'm begging you!
Mm.
Looks like my back's all crooked.
Must be from supporting this family.
You're lying. It's not crooked.
- Oh, babe.
- Hmm?
Do you think I should start teaching
at the university?
Are they still trying to rope you in?
Do whatever you want, babe. I don't mind.
But hey,
my back's still sexy, right?
- What?
- Yeah.
Definitely.
You still got it. Yeah.
- Let's leave a souvenir.
- Whoa! Careful.
Ah! Ah!
- You can't… Come on. Watch it.
- Hang on!
You're gonna ruin it. Please?
- Seriously?
- I like it.
You gotta keep it.
Promise me.
Is that her?
Is that who you drew?
Did you love Ki-dae?
OH SEO-WON
The number
you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
The number
you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
MS. OH SEO-WON
You're looking for Seo-won?
Yes.
She left with a suitcase a few days ago.
Where was she headed?
I don't know.
She didn't say.
Thanks.
You're her, right?
You're the wife?
Do you realize how much she suffered
after being questioned like that?
Why are you here?
You think you can bypass procedure
and just pop up unannounced?
- You're not prosecuting her case.
- I wouldn't show up like this if I was.
To be honest, I'm just visiting right now.
You're here as a private citizen?
Then you can't do this.
I wouldn't be here
without the defendant's blessing.
I just… didn't think her lawyer
would show up for this.
I don't know if you've heard.
An Yun-su broke her probation.
She left her house
in the middle of the night.
That was enough to revoke her bail
and send her right back here, but--
Okay, but what does any of this
have to do with my client?
Luckily, she ended up
getting caught by the police.
She said she was running after someone
who broke into her yard.
And who was it?
We're all trying to answer that.
Who did she wanna catch
so bad that she would
leave her precious daughter alone
and risk coming back
to this prison?
And all of this took place
while you were unaccounted for.
What's the question?
It's not a question.
I just thought you should know. That's it.
You're curious about
what An Yun-su's been up to out there.
That's why you had your attorney
deliver your letter to her
and got him to exchange information
with her representation.
Contact between coconspirators
is forbidden, as you know.
Who are you calling coconspirators?
That's an incredibly one-sided assertion.
It's a rational suspicion…
that's becoming clearer by the day.
I wonder why though.
Why you would come
all this way just to feel me out?
And who was it that An Yun-su
was chasing that night?
I think you should
leave my lawyer out of it.
He's already having a tough time
dealing with his client.
I think we're done here.
Our meeting is over.
I know you suspect both of them.
I get it, but
I don't know why you're trying
to poke a reaction out of her.
I assume you took her case
because of some principle
that even the worst maniacs
deserve representation.
That attitude you people have,
thinking you're the only ones out here
trying to do good,
well, I think it's fucking disgusting.
I don't know what role
you think you can play here.
It's kind of sad, really.
Come on, Counselor. Your client's waiting.
Can you confirm
that you had nothing to do with this?
What?
That person An Yun-su said
she saw in her backyard.
Are you saying
that I somehow left this place?
No, I'm not. Now that I think of it.
Then what?
I didn't take you for that type.
But you have quite
the sense of imagination, don't you?
It's just that
Ms. An seems genuinely anxious.
Oh.
Stop.
278, 3392, get in.
Walk.
Should I take you home?
Focus will be on the dentist couple
in today's hearings,
so you might wanna skip this one.
- I can just go on my own.
- No, I…
I wanna see.
If you're here
to observe the trial, line up over here.
- If you're press or involved in the trial…
- That's it.
- …proceed to Courtroom 501.
- This way.
If you have a gallery pass,
head to Courtroom 502 for the video feed.
Arms out, please.
Make sure you're in
the right line. Over here. Thank you.
Last time, your jacket was quite wrinkled.
I tried to pick something similar enough.
You don't like it?
No, I just
prefer my own.
Fine.
I appreciate it.
This way.
You're all right?
An Yun-su. She preferred to stay
with her lawyer in the other room.
There are too many reporters in here.
How can you tell who I'm looking for?
I bumped into her when I came in.
What about the victim's family?
Are they here?
Uh, only the grandfather.
Yeah, he's in room 2 as well.
Why?
You have something to tell them, Ms. Mo?
Over here. Yeah, right here.
Hello.
- Hello.
- How are you?
The court is now in session. All rise.
Please be seated.
The defense may now make
their opening statement.
Thank you.
Not long ago,
I posed a question to the defendant.
I asked her what she wanted from me.
Her response was simple.
"Can you please sit next to me
until the trial is over?"
Truth is,
there's not a lot I can do for her.
I'll admit it.
The crime she committed
was incredibly brutal and grotesque.
That's a fact.
She knew that pleading for leniency
would be out of the question.
However, I still decided
to stand before you today,
to ensure that the defendant
has the chance to reflect
on what she's done
for the rest of her life.
Because there's one thing
she deserves more than death.
And that's the right to live.
- There's not much time left.
- The defendant has disclosed her crimes.
Don't try and get smart now. Will you?
Don't try and get smart now.
There's not much time left.
Hold on!
Ms. Mo, what did you just say?
You mouthed something to the camera.
I saw you.
- Your Honor.
- What was it? What were you saying?
Your Honor, he's meddling
with the opening statement.
As you know,
speaking from the gallery is forbidden.
Who were you saying that to?
Request a review of the footage.
Prosecutor Baek, take your seat, now.
Your Honor,
I'm requesting a review of the footage.
What?
There's not much time left.
- Time?
- Don't try and get smart now.
Need me to say it again?
There's not much time left.
Don't try and get smart now.
Silence in court.
Ms. Mo.
What is the meaning of this?
Who were you speaking to,
and what did you mean by it?
Objection. This matter
is not pertinent to the case.
The remark was made
while we were in session.
Whether it's relevant or not
is for me to determine.
Ms. Mo.
Answer the question.
I don't think it would be appropriate.
Are you sure you want me to
say it here?
There's not much time left.
Don't try and get smart now.